keepbusy.net 2007-12-10

# Privacy Policy - KeepBusy.net - Keep Busy with Games and Videos

**Privacy Policy for KeepBusy.net**  
We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
Any personal information that you provide to our web site shall stay absolutely safe, private, and secure. We do not resell personal information to outside sources. 

**INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY LOGGED**  
Like almost every other web site, our systems may log information including your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. 

**COOKIES**  
Our web site may use cookies to store information about your visits. In addition, during the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. 

**EMAIL NEWSLETTER**  
Our newsletter is strictly run as an "opt-in" newsletter. We never send unsolicited emails. 

**SECURITY**  
We have taken the appropriate steps and followed industry standards to secure any personal data stored by our systems. 

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING**  
Our web site works with third parties that serve ads to this site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

**EXTERNAL LINKS**  
This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**CONTACTING OUR WEB SITE**  
If you have any comments or questions about this privacy statement or any other issues you can [contact us](mailto:admin@keepbusy.net).
